torrent.com 2005-05-28

# Enterprise Data Integration - Privacy Policy - Ascential

## Privacy Policy

### Ascential Software Privacy Policy for Ascentialsoftware.com

This statement discloses the privacy practices of Ascentialsoftware.com, the corporate Web site of Ascential Software Corporation. Ascential will seek to comply with applicable data protection laws and regulations. As a company, we want to build user trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we are disclosing to you our information practices. This includes notifying you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours - including your name, mailing address and email address - is collected from you through the Web site
  2. The organization that is collecting and holding the information 
  3. How personally identifiable information is used 
  4. With whom personally identifiable information may be shared 
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information and the consequences to you if we do not receive certain information from you 
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Ascential's control 

Please note as well that you have the right to obtain a copy of data or personally identifiable information processed or held by Ascential, and you may request to review data, change data, require rectification of inaccurate data, or require deletion of your data, and/or object to its processing under certain circumstances, by giving written notice to Ascential's Corporate Data Privacy officer at [eu-data-privacy@ascentialsoftware.com](mailto:eu-data-privacy@ascentialsoftware.com)

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or the use of your information, contact: The Web Team at [ascentialweb@ascentialsoftware.com ](mailto:ascentialweb@ascentialsoftware.com)

### Information Collection and Use

Ascential Software Corporation collects and holds the information collected on this site. Ascential is the sole owner of the information collected on this site and will keep the information for a limited period of time that is necessary for the purpose for which it is collected. We will not use this information, or sell, share, rent or otherwise disclose this information to others in ways other than as described in this statement. 

### Registration

In order to use some of the facilities accessible through this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give his or her contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. We may not be able to provide information regarding our services if a user does not provide this information. By completing the registration, the user confirms he/she has been advised on the purpose for which the information will be used and consents to such use. The user agrees to be bound by this statement, as in effect from time to time, and any other agreement provided on this Web site. 

### Our WW Practices 

Ascential Software Corporation is a global organization, with legal entities, business processes, management structures, and technical systems that cross borders. Our privacy practices are designed to seek to provide protection for your personal information, all over the world. We may share your information within Ascential and transfer it to members of the Ascential global organization and our partners in other countries in the world where we do business. Although some countries may provide less legal protection for you information, in such countries Ascential will still handle your information in the manner described here. We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its quality. We therefore implement appropriate measures and processes to help us to keep your information secure and to maintain its quality. 

### Mergers and Acquisitions

Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, Ascential decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganise businesses in some countries. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personally identifiable information to prospective or actual purchasers, or receiving it from prospective or actual sellers. It is Ascential's practice to take reasonable steps to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions. You should be aware, however, that Ascential takes no responsibility for actions taken, or any inactions, by any prospective or actual purchasers or sellers who receive such information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. After a user closes his or her browser, cookies may stay active for a period of 14 days so users do not have to reenter registration information. If a user rejects the cookie, he or she may still use our site. The principal drawback to rejecting a cookie is that the user will have only limited access to certain areas of our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### Sharing

We will not share aggregated demographic information that may contain personally identifiable information with our partners. However, we do partner with third parties who provide specific systems integration or data management services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share personally identifiable information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. 

### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Ascential is not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users in connection with surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose the information requested. Information requested may include personally identifiable information, such as name, mailing address and email address, as well as demographic information, such as zip code. It may also include other personal identifiable information. The information may also be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site, or collection of information relative to our customers or market. 

### Direct Marketing

We may use the user's personally identifiable information for marketing purpose. If you do not want to participate in our direct marketing program, please send an email to [ascentialweb@ascentialsoftware.com](mailto:ascentialweb@ascentialsoftware.com). 

### Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

If you have any questions about the security at our Web site, you can send an email to [ascentialweb@ascentialsoftware.com](mailto:ascentialweb@ascentialsoftware.com). 

### Notification of Changes

This Privacy Policy will be updated from time to time. Ascential's updated privacy statement is posted on this Web site, within a reasonable period of time, so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

Return to Terms and Conditions

For more information call 1-800-966-9875 or contact us
